Karan Bajaj

Senior Frontend Developer at Apple

Summary

Experienced Senior Frontend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the consumer electronics industry. Skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, AngularJs, JavaServer Pages (JSP), Java, and SQL. Strong engineering professional with a Master of Science (M.S.) focused in Computer Software Engineering from Carnegie Mellon University.

Experience

Senior Frontend Developer at Apple

January 2017 - Present

Graduate Teaching Assistant - Engineering Data Intensive Scalable Systems at Carnegie Mellon University

May 2016 - August 2016 (3 months)

Teaching Assistant for the Engineering Data Intensive Scalable Systems (17648) course offered by the Software engineering department at CMU. Responsibilities include:

- Create a fault injector software which could inject fault in AWS instances. This helps in validating the robustness of the projects submitted by the students
- Hold recitations to answer student questions and clear their doubts.
- Guide students in completing the projects and assignments.

Senior Software Engineer at Amadeus IT Group

July 2011 - July 2015 (4 years)

Education

Carnegie Mellon University

Master of Science (M.S.), Computer Software Engineering, 2015 - December 2016

Activities and Societies: CMU cricket team

Lingayas Institute of Management & Technology

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Information Technology, 2007 - 2011

Activities and Societies: College cricket Team, Fine arts committee, Invitation committee

Pratap Public school

1992 - 2007

Activities and Societies: Cricket team

Honors and Awards

Pat on the back Award, Spot Award, Pat on the back awardCricket

Karan Bajaj

Senior Frontend Developer at Apple



Contact Karan on LinkedIn